"Student Council Office"
So while we're on this topic,
after checking the condition
of older desks and chairs,
we'll see if they are worth replacing
and plan a budget...
What's the matter, Kageyama?
Are you not feeling well?
"Student Council"
"Student Council" I-I'm sorry...
I... I have to leave early today!
I-I'm sorry... I... I have
to leave early today!
Hey, Kageyama!
Nii-san! Wait, could this be from
the shock of getting rejected...?
I'm sorry.
I actually like someone else.
Wait for me, Nii-san! I'll be right there!
This is Nii-san's.
Wait...
Was he in an accident?
MOB MOB WOW! MOB MOB WOW!
I realized that my youth was grey
The root of this irritation is unknown
My brain runs parallel with this emotional train
Struggling adolescence
Don't disturb the subconscious mind
Who's that behind me?
Opposing ideas, distortion
Purge the sorrow
So, do what you can now.
My life
Finally
Break it down!!
(WANT) desire (YOUNG) and sincerity
(BURN) they begin to sprout (1) within my chest
(TRANCE) I won't awaken (CHANCE) but I want to
(STANCE) both sides of the coin
(1) are back-to-back
Accept me as I am
Conflicting freedom and relations
If they can become one
That smile will be
One and only "1"
MOB MOB WOW! MOB MOB WOW!
"Mob Psycho 100 III"
MOB MOB WOW!
One and only "1"
"Mob Psycho 100 III"
"Mob Psycho 100 "
MOB MOB WOW! MOB MOB WOW!
One and only "1"
"Mob 3
~Trauma~"
The shop...
I'm so sorry, Manager!
Damn it. I guess we aren't
enough to stop him after all.
What the--?!
Now there's an explosion behind us?
Wait, seriously?
Wh-What are you doing here...
--...Boss?
--Boss!
Well, well... It looks like you two
are making an honest living now.
Leave the rest to me.
I've come to repay my debt.
Sorry, but this will probably hurt a little.
I thought you might be in a bad mood,
but you actually seem rather well.
Or rather, you seem like
you've been liberated.
I guess you've given up on holding back.
That in itself isn't a bad thing,
but are you really the same person?
To think there'd be this
much of a difference...
Man, that was close.
Don't get your ass kicked
so easily, old man!
You could've died!
Sho... What are you doing here?
I'm helping my good-for-nothing dad
do some good for society.
I am your son, after all.
Huh? Wait, that's...
It's Kageyama Shigeo.
He's lost control of his powers,
and something has been
unleashed from within him.
Seriously? I don't know how I feel
about fighting Ritsu's bro.
But being gentle won't do
any good in this situation.
Can't say I've actually
ever seen you be gentle.
A direct hit?!
Dad! Hey, you okay?
Calm down.
I just needed to borrow some of his powers
to make up for the massive gap.
So you got hit on purpose?
This fight has only just begun.
Are you going to help me, Sho?
You got a plan?
If he continues to unleash energy at that rate,
he will eventually run out of stamina.
We just need to buy some
time until he stops.
So we're trying to get
him to run outta gas.
Got it.
Nii-san.
Ever since that incident, we've stopped
speaking our minds with each other.
Feeling responsible changed my brother.
He used to get mad and laugh...
When we were little,
he would let his emotions show.
But then, he stopped willingly
showing his powers.
This version of him was created from
being suppressed and locked away.
They're connected deep down
and cannot be separated.
We have to continue living
with him from now on, too.
Teru-san?!
Follow my lead.
I know!
Have a nice flight!
Charge Bomb!
Seriously?
So that's his play.
Wait, wait, wait.
He just sucked up everything we had.
Damn it!
The hell do you think you're doing?
H-Hey...
We can't even buy some time?
This is beyond us!
Let's get the hell outta here!
It's futile.
I'm not going to be able to escape,
wounded like this.
Something's wrong.
What the hell's going on?
He's... struggling?
Is he... fighting back inside?
I guess Ritsu's bro is still fighting...
...against his out-of-control powers.
You really are strong.
This is our best chance.
Sho, you need to run away.
What?! What about you?
There's one way to stop him.
I will become a vessel
and absorb all of his energy.
I just need to do what he did for me last time.
That again?
That's insane. You're going to break.
That's fine. If I sacrifice myself--
The hell are you talking--
I'm prepared for this.
Dad.
I'm sorry.
It seems I can't be as strong as you are.
Sho, will you lend me your shoulder?
Let's flee.
This is worse than we thought.
Even Suzuki couldn't get the job done.
Let's go grab him.
Yes, sir.
Dropping the guide drones.
Psychic powers are terrifying.
I guess he already knew
that this power was taboo.
Yeah, I know. I won't use mine anymore.
Living normally is the most
important thing, right?
It's difficult... But that's what
he's done this whole time.
What's going to happen to that guy now?
No one will be able to stop him.
You've gone way too far, Nii-san...
Kageyama!
So you are still here.
We're here to help you!
Let's take shelter at the gym together!
That is Kageyama... right?
Answer us, damn it!
That was no ordinary gust of wind, was it?
I believe that Kageyama must be in
some kind of sleepwalking state.
Yeah, I think so.
Which means...
We definitely can't leave him alone.
Body Improvement...
Fight on!
He just brushed us off like flies...
Does this mean that Kageyama-kun...
...was this powerful without us
even realizing it?
But, you know... we always look up to
how you usually are, too, Kageyama-kun.
So could you consider going back to normal?
Stop!
This is dangerous.
So you really are in that state.
It's been a while.
Nii-san.
I've always been terrified
about this happening.
I've been cowering all this time,
wondering when that alternate version
of you would appear again.
I hate it.
But I'm not scared anymore.
I finally figured it out.
This isn't a separate, scary version of you.
It's a part of you.
So there's no reason to be scared.
There's no reason to tremble
at the sight of it.
Because I'm...
...your younger brother.
No, Ritsu. You're wrong!
That's not me!
Ritsu, you need to...
...get away from that thing!
Nii-san.
You don't need to suffer alone like this.
Is something wrong?
I'll be happy to listen
if something's bothering you.
Nope, I'm fine! Thanks, though.
The truth was... I wanted us to talk it out.
But looking back on it now...
... guess you were holding something in
that you couldn't tell me...
...by putting a lid on your powers.
I don't want to hurt him.
At this rate, the same thing will...
But I don't want you to
change anymore, Nii-san.
Don't try to bear this on your own.
I'm here for you!
I can't hold him any longer!
I can't move! My powers don't
stand a chance against him!
Are you telling me that there's
nothing I can do for Nii-san...?
Please, stop... You're my powers, right?
That's enough! Listen to me!
It's not stopping... Ritsu's in danger.
If this continues...
If he ends up hurting Takane-san, too...
...he won't be able to bear it.
Then I'll just have to...
That's it.
I'm sure that some shock
will cause a change.
I'm sorry, Nii-san.
No!
He shouldn't be held down by trauma!!
The thing I can do for you, Nii-san...
...is continue being the little brother
you can talk to at any time.
It's to become the little brother
you can speak your mind with!
"Ritsu" It's to become the little
brother you can speak your mind with!
"Ritsu"
I finally figured it out.
The reason I wanted powers...
...was for this moment!
You'll be okay now, Nii-san.
No! Stop!
"Breaking News"
"A Giant Twister Emerges in Seasoning City"
"Breaking News" "A Giant Twister Emerges in Seasoning City"
A giant tornado has now appeared inside Seasoning City.
A giant tornado has now appeared
inside Seasoning City.
It continues to slowly move
along, surging eerily.
Why are these things occurring
in the same region,
and why are they happening
one after another?
According to some experts,
there are theories that this is the result
of some top secret science project,
and some suspect that this
is the work of psychics.
According to the emergency press
conference held by the government,
no government agencies
are involved with these--
There's no entry beyond this point.
You can't come in.
H-Hey!
Hold it!
I guess that was about all I could do...
Come back to us, Nii-san...
Found you.
What are you? Why are you doing this?
I am me. I'm Kageyama Shigeo.
Who are you supposed to be?
Huh? I'm Kageyama Shigeo...
Ah, so you're "Mob."
The fake me.
You're the fake one here.
I don't need these powers anymore.
I need you to disappear from within me.
Then you should just disappear.
I will live freely.
I will stop you.
No one can stop me.
Is it just me, or do you feel sluggish, too?
It might be dangerous to go any farther.
But Mob's in the center
of that tornado, right?
Probably...
But I'm not sure if we'll make it out
in one piece even if we get there...
You just need to help me get there. Please.
All right. I'll do everything that I can.
All right, let's go!
Why are you doing this?
Do you remember being hit by a car?
I couldn't move anymore
with just my body alone.
That's why I had to move
through sheer will.
What are you talking about?
This isn't my will at all.
You have a very strong desire
to go see Tsubomi-chan.
That is the most important thing to me.
But that's...
That's not something you should be
doing at the cost of harming others.
This isn't normal.
What is normal? Are you trying
to invalidate me once again?
If you just break and disappear,
I won't have to hold back anymore.
I'm going to do what I want.
The next time you wake up...
...I will be me.
Goodbye, Mob.
There was a blue light shining
I'm wide awake this 1:30 AM
What remained even after I swiped
Are the smiles of my friends right beside me
Yes, I want someone to understand...
This wish that's hidden colorless and invisible
The breath I was holding deep within my heart
I let it all out at once and return to my senses
On days that I'm feeling apathetic
it suddenly comes to mind
These seasons I spent as if they were a given
Even if reality becomes sullied
Only the sky we saw together is real
This is more incomprehensible
Than the grammar on the blackboard
If it's going to disappear within 24 hours
This flowing story is just too lonely
I just can't do it
Just like that back hip circle I gave up on
But I'm not going to...
Give up
My present anymore
I adorn my overflowing emotions
And run through my worries and hesitations
It can't be decided from 0 to 100
Draw the incomplete future with this hand
We can't even prove its existence
But as the world stabs the middle of my chest
It overflows with cobalt blue
English Translator: Michelle Tymon Translation Editor:
Zachary Carlysle Translation Checker: Sriram Gurunathan
Hey, Mob. Wait...
Listen to me!
There's something... I need to tell you!
Next time on Mob Psycho 100 Il Episode 12:
"Confession
~The Future~."
"Confession ~The Future~"
"Confession ~The Future~."
"Confession
~The Future~"